and we would like to begin pre-boarding
with our first class passengers first
class passengers only
please next our business class
passengers may now
board okay now we would like to welcome
our Regal Alliance Elite members Regal
Alliance Elite
members okay now all passengers with
children anyone with small children you
may board
now okay we would like to continue
boarding with uniformed military
personnel what why get this is thank you
for your service thank you so much for
your service God bless you thank you for
your service thank you for your service
all right people in
wheelchairs any priests nuns rabbis IMS
what why do they get special treatment
asalam alikum I've never